All the windows were blown out.
The lobby looked like the plane hit the lobby.
I think a problem went off the lobby first,
then a plane hit the building.
Then another plane hit the other building.
But when I was coming through the doors,
on the other side of the trade center,
something either that blew the lobby up
or something because it blew the glass out of the doors
and knocked the sword down,
and I got a smoke and everything on there.
I just feel a little shook up because I got blasted.
That's several accounts that the lobby blew up
before the first plane,
and that the subway was filled with smoke.
How is this never mentioned?
And what about the FDNY?
According to the firefighters who were in the towers,
there were bombs going off all over these buildings.
I demand to know, as should everyone,
especially the media,
why important testimony made that day
from over 150 police firefighters
and first responders regarding explosions
wasn't included in the commission report,
nor investigated further.
What happened?
It was an explosion.
It was in the lobby,
and it was the third explosion,
the whole lobby collapsed on us.
What was it like?
It was horrible.
It was like hell.
The whole building just collapsed on us inside the lobby.
Is that a secondary explosion?
Yes, it was.
That was the final problem.
Yeah, definitely a secondary explosion,
because there was inside waiting to go upstairs,
and on the way upstairs,
the whole fucking plane blew.
I mean, just collapsed from everybody inside the lobby.
So we took the first tower coming down,
second door.
I don't know about the first one,
but I know the second one was telling me.
Then there was a third one, too, after that one.
There was explosions.
I mean, there was a couple explosions.
Yeah, while we were in the building,
we were one of the first stairwells.
A real couple of times we dove into the stairway,
and we do another plane was coming.
We made it outside.
We made it about a block.
We made it at least two blocks,
and we started not.
All my bullets that are popping out.
It was like it was just a hit for the head's detonate.
Yeah, detonate it.
Yeah.
And you heard the boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo.
New York's bravest.
Never had a change.
It really never even got close to the building.
The explosion blew, and it knocked everybody over.
Five minutes in the elevators exploded us.
Yeah.
We said something's wrong.
We made the plane hit up on the 88th floor.
I mean, five minutes over.
Now the elevators exploded on the first level of water.
There was a secondary explosion,
probably a device you'd have planted before,
or on a aircraft that would not explode until now or later.